let questions = [{
        numb: 1,
        question: " What does IoT stand for?",
        answer: " Internet of Things ",
        options: [
            " Internet of Things ",
            " Internet of Technology ",
            " Internet of Telecommunications ",
            " Internet of Time "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: " Which statement best describes IoT?",
        answer: " A network of physical objects that are connected and exchange data ",
        options: [
            " A global network of interconnected humans ",
            " A network of physical objects that are connected and exchange data ",
            " A network of autonomous robots ",
            " A network of fictional devices in science fiction literature "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: " Which technology is fundamental for IoT devices to communicate with each other and the internet?",
        answer: " Wi-Fi ",
        options: [
            " Wi-Fi ",
            " Bluetooth ",
            " RFID ",
            " All of the above "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: " What is the primary goal of IoT?",
        answer: " To make all devices smart ",
        options: [
            " To make all devices smart ",
            " To connect every device to the internet ",
            " To replace human interactions with automated processes ",
            " To increase the cost of technology "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: " What does RFID  stand for in IoT?",
        answer: " Radio Frequency Identification ",
        options: [
            " Radio Frequency Identification ",
            " Remote File Download ",
            " Randomized Frequency Integration Device ",
            " Real-time Feedback and Identification "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: " Which IoT component is responsible for collecting data from the physical world?",
        answer: " Edge device ",
        options: [
            " Edge device ",
            " Cloud server ",
            " Data visualization tool ",
            " IoT gateway "
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 7,
        question: " What is the term for an IoT device that is directly connected to the internet, typically through Wi-Fi or cellular networks?",
        answer: " Edge device ",
        options: [
            " Edge device ",
            " IoT gateway ",
            " Cloud server ",
            " Sensor node "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: " Which wireless technology is commonly used for short-range communication between IoT devices?",
        answer: " Zigbee ",
        options: [
            " Zigbee ",
            " 4G ",
            " LoRa ",
            " Satellite "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: " What is a common use case of IoT in the healthcare industry?",
        answer: " Remote patient monitoring ",
        options: [
            " Remote patient monitoring ",
            " Smart refrigerators ",
            " Weather forecasting ",
            " Virtual reality gaming "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: " What is the Smart home concept in IoT?",
        answer: " A home equipped with devices and systems that can be remotely monitored and controlled ",
        options: [
            " A house that can think and make decisions for its occupants. ",
            " A home equipped with devices and systems that can be remotely monitored and controlled ",
            " A home with advanced security systems ",
            " A house that can fix itself "
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Which IoT communication protocol is widely used for real-time data exchange in industrial applications?",
        answer: " MQTT ",
        options: [
            " MQTT ",
            " HTTP ",
            " FTP ",
            " SMTP "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: " What is the primary concern regarding IoT security?",
        answer: " Data privacy and protection ",
        options: [
            " Data privacy and protection ",
            " Device size and weight ",
            " Energy efficiency ",
            " Device compatibility "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: " What is a sensor node in IoT?",
        answer: " A small device that collects data from the environment and transmits it to a central system ",
        options: [
            " A small device that collects data from the environment and transmits it to a central system ",
            " A complex computer used for data analysis in the cloud ",
            " A device that connects IoT devices to the internet ",
            " A type of IoT gateway "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: " What does AI stand for in the context of IoT?",
        answer: " Artificial Intelligence ",
        options: [
            " Advanced Integration ",
            " Artificial Intelligence ",
            " Automated Interaction ",
            " Adaptive Infrastructure "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: " Which IoT application is focused on improving transportation and traffic management?",
        answer: " Connected vehicles ",
        options: [
            " Smart agriculture ",
            " Intelligent healthcare ",
            " Connected vehicles ",
            " Smart homes  "
        ]
    },
]